[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：好的，让我们看看addg。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Okay, let's look at addg.
Addg接受第一个参数，它创建了一个more函数。
Addg takes a first argument, it creates a more function.
如果第一个参数没有定义，则返回more函数。
If the first argument is not undefined it returns the more function.
如果未定义下一个参数，则More函数接受下一个参数
The more function takes the next argument If the next argument is undefined
它首先返回，否则它添加到第一个并返回自身。
it returns first otherwise it adds next to first and returns itself.
通过返回本身允许
By returning itself allows for
接下来发生的事情，我称之为这个返回递归。
the next thing to happen and I call this return recursion.
递归是指具有调用自身的函数
Recursion is when you have a function that calls itself
递归是当您有一个返回自身的函数时。
recursion is when you have a function that returns itself.
还有人做了什么吗？
So anybody do anything else?
采取不同的方法来解决这个问题？
Take a different approach to solving this?
有很多可能的解决方案。
There are lots of possible solutions.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你在做同样的事情，你提前计算下一个值。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're doing the same thing where you compute ahead the next value.
那个你，你昨天在另一个地方做了另一个。
That you, you did it in another part another one yesterday.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以如果你没有得到这个，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So if you didn't get this one,
请把它写下来，因为我们下一次需要它。
please write it down cuz we're gonna need it for the next one.
还有人吗？
Anybody else?
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：嗯，这是不同的，我不知道怎么读和说。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Well, it is different and I don't know how to read it and say that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：效果未定义，返回undefined。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The effects is undefined, return undefined.
我不知道，我什么也看不到，没关系，继续走。
I don't know, I don't see anything, never mind, keep going.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：好的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: All right.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以我给你一分钟来捕捉这一点。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So I'll give you a minute to capture this.
所以在发生这件事的时候，有人能猜出这个名字吗？
So while that's happening can anyone guess the name
对于我们应该编写的下一个函数&gt；&gt；Speaker 3：Lift g，
of the next function that we should write &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Lift g,
道格拉斯·克罗克福德：是的，非常好，
lift g &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah very very good,
当然，举起g。
lift g, of course.
接下来你还想写什么？
What else would you want to write next?
编写一个函数Liftg。
Write a function liftg.
这将接受一个二进制函数并将其应用于许多调用。
That will take a binary function and apply it to many invocations.
所以它与我们以前做过的类似。
So it's similar to what we've done before.
如果您将add函数传递给liftg，它将为您提供Aggi函数。
If you pass the add function to liftg it gives you the Aggi function.
我们可以用乘法做同样的事情，你做多功能。
We can do the same thing with multiply you make the multifunction.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：如果您传递了add into liftg，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: If you passed add into liftg,
第一次操作的价值是多少？
what would the value of the first operation be?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你第一次打电话会得到什么？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What would you get back from the first time you call?
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：未定义。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：未定义。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Undefined. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It would be undefined.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：好吧，如果你要调用结果-
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Well if you were to call the resulting-
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不，而不是传入
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, instead of passing in
穆尔，你传给阿德。
mul, you pass in add.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对，虽然这样你得到一个未定义的，你得到3，然后
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right, although so you get an undefined, you get 3, and
然后你会得到7个。
then you’ll get 7.
然后你会在表格上得到7和0。
And then you'll get 7 and 0 against the form.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你得到3，0。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You got 3, 0.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：但是如果使用mul，则是3乘以1。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: But with mul you’re multiplying 3 times 1.
好吧。&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：好的，那么
Okay. &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: All right so
这里是liftg，liftg返回一个函数，
here is liftg, liftg returns a function,
该函数获取第一个参数，如果未定义First，则返回First。
that function gets the first argument if first is undefined it returns first.
否则，它将返回more函数。
Otherwise it returns the more function.
more函数获取next参数，如果未定义next，则它首先返回。
The more function gets the next argument if next is undefined it returns first.
否则，它将FIRST设置为带有FIRST和的二进制函数的结果
Otherwise it sets first to the result of the binary function with first and
下一个并返回自身。
next And returns itself.
那么，谁得到的东西，工作出色，非常好。
So who got something that works outstanding very very good.
关于这个的任何问题，
Any questions about this one,
任何人做一个不同的方法
anybody do a different approach that
他们认为值得一提的是。
they think is worth mentioning.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我做得很好，但我尝试了第一个选项编号。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I do a great work but I tried First option number.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对，所以如果你没有得到这个，就把它放下来。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right so if you didn't get this one get it down.
您可能想在下一篇文章中引用它。
You might want to refer to it in the next one.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：这当然还不错
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: This is certainly good yet
您可以在新函数内部执行函数，并泛化。
you function inside Inside the new function and generalize the.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：ig功能。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The ig function.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以如果您第一次在没有任何内容的情况下调用它
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So the first time if you call this with nothing
然后你会，你传入未定义的
then you would, you pass in undefined
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：你只要找回自己。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You just get back itself.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：对，我们返回undefined so。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Right we return undefined so.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：下次当你，所以如果你传入一个数字。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The next time when you, so if you pass in a number.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这个数字现在是第一
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: That number is now first and
然后第二次，如果我们没有定义，我们首先返回。
then the second time if we get undefined we return first.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：号码现在是我看到的第一个。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The number is now First I see.
是的很好。
Yeah great.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：编写一个函数组G，它将构建一个数组
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Write a function array G that will build an array for
许多调用，所以如果我们调用数组G并且不传递任何内容，它将返回一个空数组。
many invocations So if we call array Gand pass it nothing It returns an empty array.
如果我们传递给它三个，然后为空，它返回包含三个的数组。
If we pass it three and then nothing it returns array containing three.
如果我们把它传递给三，然后是四，然后是五，没有返回三，
If we pass it through three and then four and then five, and nothing returns three,
四和五。
four and five.
好，这里是arrayg，arrayg接受第一个参数，它创建一个数组。
Okay so here is arrayg, arrayg takes a first argument, it creates an array.
它使一个更多的功能和
It makes a more function and
它返回使用第一个参数调用more函数的结果。
it returns the result of calling the more function with the first argument.
more函数获取next参数，如果未定义next，则返回Array。
The more function gets the next argument if next is undefined it returns the Array.
否则，它将下一个参数推送到Array上，并返回自身。
Otherwise it pushes the next argument onto the Array, and returns itself.
那么谁有用的东西呢？
So who got something that works?
非常好。
Very good, very good.
有人试过用升降机吗？
Did anybody try using liftg?
有人吗？
Anyone?
那就有额外的学分了。
That would have an extra credit all right.
所以我们再来一次。
So let's do another one.
好的，我们知道了，我知道了，这对你来说是个不错的选择。
Okay we've I've got got this is a good one for you.
使函数Continuize采用酉函数并
Make a function continuize that takes a unitary function and
返回接受回调和参数的函数。
returns a function that takes a callback and an argument.
有一种编程风格叫做延续传递风格。
There's a style of programming called continuation passing style.
其中函数不是返回值，
In which functions, instead of returning values,
取而代之的是提供一个额外的参数，该参数是要传递到的函数
instead are given an additional argument which is the function to which to deliver
该值和延续传递样式的计算总是向前发展，
that value and in continuation passing style computation is always going forward,
函数往往不返回任何内容。
functions tend not to return anything.
他们总是向前走，这是令人惊异的。
They're always going forward and it's amazing.
当JavaScript获得ES6的尾递归时，
And when JavaScript gets tail recursion with ES6,
然后我们将能够在JavaScript中实现这一点，这将是非常棒的。
then we'll be able to do that in JavaScript and that will be great.
因此，此函数旨在帮助我们迁移到这种编程风格。
So this function is intended to help us to migrate toward that style of programming.
所以它所做的就是允许我们将任何现有的一元函数
So what it'll do is Allow us to take any existing unary function and
将其转换为将接受回调的函数。
turn it into a function that will take a call back.
所以在这种情况下，我们将传递平方根函数以继续WISE，
So in this case we're gonna pass the square root function to continue wise,
它将使用回调函数返回平方根。
it will return the square root with a callback function.
然后我们将调用该函数，并传入一个将接收结果的函数。
We will then call that function passing in a function that will receive the result.
在这种情况下，我建议它可能是Alert函数，它是
In this case I'm suggesting that it could be the Alert function, which is something
它存在于浏览器中，它将弹出一个框并向您显示答案。
that lives in the browser, which will pop up a box and show you the answer.
如果您没有在浏览器中运行，您可以登录到控制台或
If you're not running in a browser you could log to the console or
不管你在做什么。
whatever you're doing.
一些仅仅是看到结果走向的某种方式。
Some just some way of seeing where the result is going to go.
然后将传入81，这是我们想要取的平方根的数字。
And then will pass in 81 which is the number we want to take the square root of.
所以如果这个函数工作正常，
So if this function is working correctly,
然后我们应该在浏览器上看到一个带有数字9的框。
then we should see a box show up on the browser with the number 9 in it.
好的，这里是Continuize，Continuize取一元函数返回
Okay, so here's continuize, continuize takes a unary function The returns
获取回调和参数并返回调用结果的函数的
of function that takes a callback and an argument and returns result of calling
带有一元函数和参数结果的回调函数。
the callback function with the result of the unary function and the argument.
那么谁有用的东西呢？
So who got something that works?
恭喜您现在已经跻身JavaScript程序员的90%行列。
Congratulations you are now in the 90% tile of JavaScript programmers.
并不是说门槛很高，而是&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]
Not that the bar was ever very high but &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：但是你在上面
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: But you're up there
这是因为你理解了语言的一个方面，
and it's because you understand an aspect of the language which is really,
非常重要，非常重要的是，大多数使用这种语言的人
really important, vitally important that most of the people working this language
不知道，甚至不知道它在那里。
don't know, don't know that it's even there.
这真的很重要。
And it's really important.
我们在过去的一天里所做的是一个范式的转变。
What we've been doing over the last day is a paradigm shift.
我可以说上几个小时
I could talk for hours and hours about
当您有一个函数返回一个函数，并返回一个函数时，会发生什么情况
what could happen when you have a function that returns a function and
你会认为你会明白这些话然后说是的但是，
you would think you would understand those words and go yeah but,
除非你已经做了几十次，否则真的不会有什么不同。
unless you've done it a few dozen times, it really won't make any difference.
这不会有任何意义，但你现在已经做到了。
It won't make any sense but you've done it now.
昨天早上你进来的时候。
When you came in here yesterday morning.
你不知道如何写这个函数。
You did not know how to write this function.
你刚刚把它敲下来了。
And you just knocked it off.
你写得很快，而且写对了。
You wrote it very quickly and you got it right.
对你太好了。
So good for you.
我们经历这一切的原因是我想再次向你解释
And the reason we went through all of this is that I wanted to explain to you again
我在第一天做的事情，你以为你明白了，但你没有。
something that I did on the first day that you thought you understood but you didn't.
所以，我们要再来一遍。
So, we're going to go through that again.
现在和这一次，您已经有了上下文的工具
Now and this time you now have the tools of the context
为了理解我在说什么
in order to understand what I was talking about